Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
8094
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-
600 cubic feet.
Vinyl records and other A/V Recordings, Financial Records, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Photocopies, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Afrika Bambaataa is an American disc jockey, singer, and songwriter from the South Bronx, New York. Often called the “Godfather” of Hip Hop, Bambaataa has helped to define Hip Hop since it emerged in the South Bronx in the 1970s. One of a handful of Hip Hop's 1970s originators, Bambaataa gave Hip Hop its name, and was the first to define its core artistic elements - DJing, rapping, break dancing, and graffiti art - under one cultural umbrella. His cultural organization, the Universal Zulu Nation, has helped to spread Hip Hop culture throughout the world. His genre-defining 1982 song "Planet Rock" and subsequent electro-funk tracks have become icons of hip-hop and electronic music. In 2007 he was nominated for induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-; Universal Zulu Nation (Organization)
Subjects:
African American youth -- Social life and customs.; Disc jockeys.; Electronic music.; Funk (Music).; Hip-hop.; Hip-hop -- Influence.; Hip-hop -- History. -- United States; Music -- Social aspects.; Race relations.; Rap (Music); Rap (Music) -- Political aspects.; Rap musicians.; Hip-hop -- New York.; Rap (Music) -- New York.; Hip-hop; Rap (Music); Rap musicians; Social history
Places:
Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 20th century.; New York (State) -- New York; New York (State) -- Bronx; United States
Form and Genre Terms:
History
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to collection restricted until completion of processing, with the exception of vinyl records that have been individually cataloged.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Manuscripts
a. School Papers and Assignments
b. Africa Trip
c. Soul Scrapbooks and Music Writing
d. Notebooks and Miscellaneous Manuscripts
e. Lyrics and Poems
f. Bronx River Neighborhood Center
g. Phone and Contact Lists
Series II. Flyers
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Personal Papers
a. Personal Papers
b. Press About Bambaataa
c. Catalogs and Mail
Series V. Universal Zulu Nation Documents
a. Infinity Lessons
b. Administration
Series VI. Stage Costumes and Clothing
Series VII. Periodicals and Publications
a. Small Press Publications
b. Periodicals
c. Publications from 3410 De Reimer Ave. Bronx, NY
d. Other Publications
Series VIII. Moving images and audio recordings
a. Video cassettes
a. Audio cassettes
Series IX. Music collection
12 inch vinyl
Sureshots and altered/obscured
Numbered by Bambaataa
Annotated, not numbered (Alphabetical by artist)
A-D
E-H
I-L
L-O
P-S
T-Z
Numbers, unknown and various
Second alpha sequence
Cataloged individually
Not annotated (Alphabetical by artist)
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
K
L
M
N
O
P
Q
R
S
Afrika Bambaataa recordings
Renegades of Rhythm Tour
Test pressings and white labels (not yet cataloged)
Compilations (not yet cataloged)
7 inch vinyl
Numbered (not yet cataloged)
Annotated not numbered (not yet cataloged)
No annotations (not yet cataloged)
Acetates and lacquer discs
Cassettes (not yet cataloged)
CDs (not yet cataloged)
Series X. Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not Annotated
      Series contains vinyl discs that are either not annotated or the annotations are small and were missed during the sorting of discs. While some effort was taken to bring together piences that were dense in copy-specific track preferences. These items are arranged in alphabetical order by artists’ last name or the name of the group. Each letter of the alphabet has a subseries. Compilations, soundtracks, and other albums with various artists are in subseries together. Artists and groups whose names start with a number are in a separate subseries. Most artists are alphabetized under the name they are most well-known as (e.g. Puff Daddy; Prince; Fela). The variations of names are contained in the Creator field. In a few cases, however, artists’ aliases were unknown, and they may have been listed under two different artist names.
      - S
        - S-Express - Theme from S-Express, 1988; SR-24055; S-Express (Box 421)
          In same jacket as # SR-24056. 2 copies.
          Catalog # LEFT 21T; A-side Matrix # LEFT-21 T-A
          Rhythm King Records
          London, United Kingdom
        - S-Express - Theme from S-Express, 1988; SR-24056; S-Express (Box 421)
          In same jacket as # SR-24055. 2 copies.
        - Sa-Deuce - Don't waste my time, 1996; SR-24057; Sa-Deuce (Box 421)
          Catalog # ED 5837; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-5837-A1
          Eastwest Records
          New York, New York
        - Sa-Fire - Let me be the one, 1987; SR-24058; Sa-Fire (Box 421)
          Catalog # CR-212; A-side Matrix # CR-212-A
          Cutting Records
        - Sa-Ra Creative - Cosmic lust, 2005; SR-24059; Sa-Ra Creative (Box 421)
          Catalog # JSV-008; A-side Matrix # JSV-008-A
          Jazzy Sport
          Tokyo, Japan
        - Sa-Ra - Glorious + rosebuds, 2004; SR-24060; Sa-Ra (Box 421)
          Catalog # ABBS8004-1; A-side Matrix # S-54996 RE-1
          ABB Soul
          Oakland, California
        - Sa-Ra Creative Partners - Double dutch (co co pops); Death of a star (supernova), 2004; SR-24061; Sa-Ra Creative Partners (Box 421)
          Catalog # UR12162; A-side Matrix # S-55937
          Ubiquity
          Costa Mesa, California
        - Saafir - Boxcar sessions (disc one), 1994; SR-24062; Saafir (Box 421)
          In same jacket as # SR-24063. Double album.
          Catalog # PRO-A-7314; A-side Matrix # PRO A1 7314-SR1
          Qwest Records
          Burbank, California
        - Saafir - Boxcar sessions (disc two), 1994; SR-24063; Saafir (Box 421)
          In same jacket as # SR-24062. Double album.
          Catalog # PRO-A-7314; A-side Matrix # PRO A3 7314-SR1
        - Saafir - Watch how daddy ball, 1999; SR-24064; Saafir (Box 421)
          Catalog # PRO-A-100193; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-100193-A-SR1
        - Saafir - Light sleeper; Battle drill, 1994; SR-24065; Saafir (Box 421)
          Catalog # PRO-A-6920; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-6920-SR1
        - Saafir - Light sleeper; Battle drill, 1994; SR-24066; Saafir (Box 421)
        - Saafir - Just riden', 1994; SR-24067; Saafir (Box 421)
          Catalog # PRO-A-7381; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-7381-A-SR1
        - Sabelle - Where did the love go (say what, say what, say what)?, 1994; SR-24068; Sabelle (Box 421)
          Catalog # TB 640; A-side Matrix # TB-640-A
          Tommy Boy
        - Sabelle - One o'clock, 1996; SR-24069; Sabelle (Box 421)
          Catalog # OAS 8726; A-side Matrix # XSS-8726A-1A
          Work
        - Sabotage - Rap é compromisso (disc one), 2002; SR-24070; Sabotage (Box 421)
          In same jacket as # SR-24071. Double album.
          Catalog # 1004-12; A-side Matrix # SABOTAGE AI
          Cosa Nostra
          São Paulo, Brazil
        - Sabotage - Rap é compromisso (disc two), 2002; SR-24071; Sabotage (Box 421)
          In same jacket as # SR-24070. Double album.
          Catalog # 1004-12; A-side Matrix # SABOTAGE AII
        - Sabres of Paradise - Duke of Earlsfield; Bubble and slide, 1995; SR-24072; Sabres of Paradise (Box 421)
          Catalog # 10WAP62; A-side Matrix # 10WAP62-A1
          Warp Records
        - Sabrina - Boys (summertime love), 1988; SR-24073; Sabrina (Box 421)
          Catalog # 0-21014; A-side Matrix # 0-21014-A SH1
          Sire
        - Sabu - Sabu, 1980; SR-24074; Sabu (Box 421)
          Catalog # MCA-3236; A-side Matrix # MCA 2176 W1
          MCA Records
          Universal City, California
        - Sacchi, Robert - Jungle queen, 1982; SR-24075; Sacchi, Robert (Box 421)
          Catalog # CPD-202; A-side Matrix # PRC-C-1-CPD-202
          Compleat Records
        - Sacco - The people theme, 1978; SR-24076; Sacco (Box 421)
          Catalog # ASD 501; A-side Matrix # XSS164896-1B
          Lifesong
        - Sade - Never as good as the first time, 1985; SR-24077; Sade (Box 421)
          Catalog # RAS 2293; A-side Matrix # XSS-175005-1A
          Portrait
        - Sade - The sweetest taboo, 1985; SR-24078; Sade (Box 421)
          Catalog # RAS 2219; A-side Matrix # XSM-174790-1A
        - Sade - Cherish the day, 1993; SR-24079; Sade (Box 421)
          In same jacket as # SR-24080. 2 copies.
          Catalog # EAS 5360; A-side Matrix # XSS5360A-1A
          Epic
        - Sade - Cherish the day, 1993; SR-24080; Sade (Box 421)
          In same jacket as # SR-24079. 2 copies.
        - Sagoo, Bally - Dil cheez (my heart), 1996; SR-24081; Sagoo, Bally (Box 421)
          Catalog # 01-663488-20; A-side Matrix # 01 663488 20 2A1
          Columbia
        - Sagoo, Bally - Dil cheez (my heart), 1996; SR-24082; Sagoo, Bally (Box 421)
          Catalog # XPR 2314; A-side Matrix # 31 2314 20 1A1
        - Sagoo, Bally - Rising from the East album sampler, 1996; SR-24083; Sagoo, Bally (Box 421)
          Catalog # XPR 2317; A-side Matrix # 31 2317 20 1A1
        - Sah-B - Some ol' Sah-B shhh, 1994; SR-24084; Sah-B (Box 421)
          Catalog # PRO-A-7198; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1/A2-7198 SR1
          Reprise Records
        - Sah-B - Summa day; Some ol' Sah-B shhh, 1994; SR-24085; Sah-B (Box 421)
          Catalog # PRO-A-7042; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-7042-SR1 RE1
        - Sah-B - Summa day; Some ol' Sah-B shhh, 1994; SR-24086; Sah-B (Box 421)
        - Sahdeeq, Shabaam - Are you ready; Concrete, 1999; SR-24087; Sahdeeq, Shabaam (Box 421)
          Catalog # RWK 197-1; A-side Matrix # RWK 197-1A RE
          Rawkus
        - Saheed - Give it to me, 1996; SR-24088; Saheed; Fadi (Box 421)
          In same jacket as # SR-24089. 2 copies.
          Catalog # GO-43; A-side Matrix # GO-43-A
          Groove On
        - Saheed - Give it to me, 1996; SR-24089; Saheed; Fadi (Box 421)
          In same jacket as # SR-24088. 2 copies.
        - Sailor - Down by the docks, 1977; SR-24090; Sailor (Box 421)
          Catalog # 12C4-8229; A-side Matrix # 8229-A-1A02HD
        - Saint Etienne - Hug my soul, 1994; SR-24091; Saint Etienne (Box 421)
          Catalog # PRO-A-7069; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-7069 SR-1
          Warner Bros Records
        - Saint Etienne - Nothing can stop us, 1992; SR-24092; Saint Etienne (Box 421)
          Catalog # 0-40395; A-side Matrix # 0-40395-A-SR1
        - Sakamoto, Riuichi - Just about enough, 1982; SR-24093; Sakamoto, Riuichi; Scott, Robin (Box 421)
          Catalog # 49-03341; A-side Matrix # XSS170683-1A
        - Sakamoto, Riuichi - You do me, 1990; SR-24094; Sakamoto, Riuichi; Jones, Jill (Box 421)
          Catalog # 0-96495; A-side Matrix # STDM 58456-58306-1
          Virgin
          Beverly Hills, California
        - Sakamoto, Riuichi - Riot in Lagos, 1981; SR-24095; Sakamoto, Riuichi (Box 421)
          Catalog # 600 679; A-side Matrix # 600679 A-1/82S 1
          Rocktopus
          Berlin, Germany
        - Sakamoto, Riuichi - Left handed dream, 1982; SR-24096; Sakamoto, Riuichi (Box 421)
          Catalog # ARE 38404; A-side Matrix # P AL 38404-1A
        - Stevie Salas Colorcode - Stevie Salas Colorcode, 1990; SR-24097; Stevie Salas Colorcode (Box 421)
          Catalog # 91303-1; A-side Matrix # STIL-897605 + DMM-1
          Island
        - Saleh, Seif Salim - Taarab 1: the music of Zanzibar, 1988; SR-24098; Saleh, Seif Salim; Ahmed, Abdullah Mussa (Box 421)
          Catalog # ORBD 032; A-side Matrix # DMC-3293 A-1/7-88
          Globe Style
          Germany
        - Salsabuster - Por que yo te amo, 1984; SR-24099; Salsabuster (Box 421)
          Catalog # 0201; A-side Matrix # TM-0201-A
          Two Musketeers Records Inc.
          Westwood, New Jersey
        - Salsoul Orchestra - Christmas jollies II, 1981; SR-24100; Salsoul Orchestra (Box 421)
          In same jacket as # SR-24101. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SA 8547; A-side Matrix # SA-8547-A
          Salsoul Records
        - Salsoul Orchestra - Christmas jollies II, 1981; SR-24101; Salsoul Orchestra (Box 421)
          In same jacket as # SR-24100. 2 copies.
        - Salsoul Orchestra - Deck the halls, 1981; SR-24102; Salsoul Orchestra (Box 421)
          Catalog # SG 358; A-side Matrix # SG-358-A
        - Salsoul Orchestra - Christmas medley, 1976; SR-24103; Salsoul Orchestra (Box 421)
          Catalog # SG 384; A-side Matrix # SG 384A
        - Salsoul Orchestra - Take some time out (for love), 1982; SR-24104; Salsoul Orchestra (Box 421)
          Catalog # SG 372; A-side Matrix # SG-372-A
        - Salsoul Orchestra - Salsoul Orchestra, 1994; SR-24105; Salsoul Orchestra (Box 421)
          Catalog # CPLP 8059; A-side Matrix # CPLP 8059 A
        - Salsoul Orchestra - Up the yellow brick road, 1978; SR-24106; Salsoul Orchestra (Box 421)
          Catalog # SA 8500; A-side Matrix # SA 8500 A
        - Salsoul Orchestra - Seconds, 1982; SR-24107; Salsoul Orchestra (Box 422)
          Catalog # SG 376; A-side Matrix # SG-376-A
        - Salsoul Orchestra - Ooh, I love it (love break), 1975; SR-24108; Salsoul Orchestra (Box 422)
          Catalog # SG 391; A-side Matrix # SG-391-A
        - Salt-N-Pepa - Shake your thang; Spinderella's not a fella (but a girl DJ), 1988; SR-24109; Salt-N-Pepa (Box 422)
          Catalog # NP50077; A-side Matrix # NP-50077-DEF-1
          Next Plateau Records Inc.
        - Salt-N-Pepa - Tramp; Push it, 1987; SR-24110; Salt-N-Pepa (Box 422)
          Catalog # CHAMP 12-51; A-side Matrix # CHAMP 1251 A1
          Champion
        - Salt-N-Pepa - None of your business, 1994; SR-24111; Salt-N-Pepa (Box 422)
          Catalog # 857-715-1; A-side Matrix # 422-857-715-1 A
          London Records
        - Salt-N-Pepa - Ain't nuthin' but a she thing, 1995; SR-24112; Salt-N-Pepa (Box 422)
          Catalog # PR12 7075-1; A-side Matrix # PR12-7075-1A
        - Salt-N-Pepa - Brand new (disc one), 1997; SR-24113; Salt-N-Pepa (Box 422)
          In same jacket as # SR-24114. Double album.
          Catalog # 422-828 959-1; A-side Matrix # 422-828-959-1A
        - Salt-N-Pepa - Brand new (disc two), 1997; SR-24114; Salt-N-Pepa (Box 422)
          In same jacket as # SR-24113. Double album.
          Catalog # 422-828 959-1; A-side Matrix # 422-828-959-1C
        - Salt-N-Pepa - Expression, 1989; SR-24115; Salt-N-Pepa (Box 422)
          Catalog # NP50101; A-side Matrix # NP-50101-A-RE-1
        - Salt-N-Pepa - Gitty up, 1998; SR-24116; Salt-N-Pepa (Box 422)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # LONDON SALT-N-PEPA GITTY UP
        - Salt-N-Pepa - Champagne, 1996; SR-24117; Salt-N-Pepa (Box 422)
          Catalog # MCA8P 3809; A-side Matrix # MCA-12664-SIDE ONE
        - Salt-N-Pepa - Get up everybody (get up), 1988; SR-24118; Salt-N-Pepa (Box 422)
          Catalog # NP50083; A-side Matrix # NP-50083 REDJ-A
        - Salt-N-Pepa - Shoop, 1993; SR-24119; Salt-N-Pepa (Box 422)
          Catalog # 857 315-1; A-side Matrix # 857-315-1-A
        - Salt-N-Pepa - I'll take your man, 1986; SR-24120; Salt-N-Pepa (Box 422)
          Catalog # NP50043; A-side Matrix # NP-50043-A
        - Samba Soul - Kriola, 1978; SR-24121; Samba Soul (Box 422)
          In same jacket as # SR-24122. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PD-11256; A-side Matrix # PD 11256A
          RCA Victor
        - Samba Soul - Kriola, 1978; SR-24122; Samba Soul (Box 422)
          In same jacket as # SR-24121. 2 copies.
        - Salter, Sam - Once my sh.., 2000; SR-24123; Salter, Sam (Box 422)
          Catalog # LFDP-4459; A-side Matrix # LFDP-4459-SA
          LaFace Records
        - Salter, Sam - Before 12, after 6, 1997; SR-24124; Salter, Sam (Box 422)
          Catalog # 73008-24266-1; A-side Matrix # 73008-24266-1-S A1
        - Saluga, Bill - Dancin' Johnson, 1978; SR-24125; Saluga, Bill (Box 422)
          Annotated.
          Catalog # SP-12018; A-side Matrix # AM 12035 DJ LONG RC1
          A&M Disco
          Santa Monica, California
        - Sam & Dave - The best of Sam & Dave, 1969; SR-24126; Sam & Dave (Box 422)
          Catalog # SD 8218; A-side Matrix # ST-A-681453-B
          Atlantic
        - Sam "The Beast" - Take it off, 1993; SR-24127; Sam "The Beast" (Box 422)
          Catalog # BR108; A-side Matrix # BR-108 A
          Siren
          United States
        - Sam "The Beast" - Gucci dance, 1994; SR-24128; Sam "The Beast" (Box 422)
          In same jacket as # SR-24129. Different discs.
          Catalog # BR109; A-side Matrix # BR-109-A
        - Sam "The Beast" - Gucci dance, 1994; SR-24129; Sam "The Beast" (Box 422)
          In same jacket as # SR-24128. Different discs.
          Catalog # 88561-1241-1; A-side Matrix # 88561-1241-1-A
          Relativity
          Jamaica, New York
        - Sam the Sham and The Pharaohs - Wooly bully, 1965; SR-24130; Sam the Sham and The Pharaohs (Box 422)
          Catalog # 2486 269; A-side Matrix # 160 2486269 A
          Polydor
          France
        - Samantha - Ring my bell, 1994; SR-24131; Samantha (Box 422)
          Catalog # YY 1001; A-side Matrix # 1001-A
          Ying Yang Records
          Miami Beach, Florida
        - Samba Soul - Do it, 1978; SR-24132; Samba Soul (Box 422)
          Catalog # APL1-2991; A-side Matrix # APL1-2991A-1
        - Sampa Crew - Sexy, 1994; SR-24133; Sampa Crew (Box 422)
          Catalog # 52.273; A-side Matrix # 52273 A
          Brazil
        - Sampa Crew - Super remixes, 1992; SR-24134; Sampa Crew (Box 422)
          Catalog # RQN031; A-side Matrix # RQN031 A
          Kaskata Records
          Sao Paulo, Brazil
        - Sampa Crew - Sampa Crew, 1994; SR-24135; Sampa Crew (Box 422)
          Catalog # 177.398; A-side Matrix # 177.398 A
        - Sampa Crew - Verdadeira paixão, 1995; SR-24136; Sampa Crew (Box 422)
          Catalog # 177.444; A-side Matrix # 777444 A III
        - Sampa Crew - Sampa Crew, 1994; SR-24137; Sampa Crew (Box 422)
        - Sampa Crew - Ritmo amor poesia, 1994; SR-24138; Sampa Crew (Box 422)
          Catalog # RQN004; A-side Matrix # RQN004 A
          Kaskatas Records
        - Sampa Crew - Eterno amor, 1994; SR-24139; Sampa Crew (Box 422)
          In same jacket as # SR-24140. Different discs.
          Catalog # 52.266; A-side Matrix # 52266 A XSLP-2293
        - Sampa Crew - Filhos da rua, 1994; SR-24140; Sampa Crew (Box 422)
          In same jacket as # SR-24139. Different discs.
          Catalog # 52.267; A-side Matrix # 52267 A XSLP-2293
        - Sanborn, David - Slam, 1988; SR-24142; Sanborn, David (Box 422)
          Catalog # 0-20965; A-side Matrix # 0-20965-A-SH-2
        - Sanchez - Something just ain't right, 1992; SR-24143; Sanchez (Box 422)
          Catalog # PW 475; A-side Matrix # PW-475-A
          Pow Wow Records
        - Sanchez, Jose - You know where I'm coming from, 2000; SR-24144; Sanchez, Jose; Angry Mexican DJ's (Box 422)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # MILF-SCATTY-002-A2
          Skatty Productions
          Gloucester, United Kingdom
        - Sancho - Chase vampire; One dolla, 1987; SR-24145; Sancho; Sweet Barry (Box 422)
          Catalog # VPRD-6360; A-side Matrix # VPRD-636-A
          VP Records
        - Sancocho - Rumba te tumba, 1997; SR-24146; Sancocho (Box 422)
          Catalog # CR-402; A-side Matrix # CR-402-A
        - Sancocho - Pon melo ahi; Como te mueve, 1997; SR-24147; Sancocho (Box 422)
          Catalog # CR-412; A-side Matrix # CR412-A
        - Sancocho - Tumba la casa, 1996; SR-24148; Sancocho (Box 422)
          Catalog # CR-383; A-side Matrix # CR-383-A
        - Sancocho - Tumba la casa, 1996; SR-24149; Sancocho (Box 422)
        - Sandals - A profound gas, 1992; SR-24150; Sandals (Box 422)
          Catalog # JAZID 47T; A-side Matrix # JAZID 47T-A2
          Open Toe Records
        - Sanders, Stephan - All the women in the world; Confectionary, 1987; SR-24151; Sanders, Stephan (Box 422)
          Catalog # MRI-203; A-side Matrix # MR-203-A
          Magnum Records International
          Liberty City, Florida
        - Sandra - Everlasting love, 1988; SR-24152; Sandra (Box 422)
          Catalog # DMD 1181; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-57141-57139 DMM-1
        - Sangria - To the beat y'all; Loose on forty duce, 1981; SR-24153; Sangria (Box 422)
          Catalog # RR-103; A-side Matrix # RR-103-A
          Real To Reel Productions
        - Sanitarium - Going crazy, 1995; SR-24153; Sanitarium (Box 422)
          Catalog # CR-328; A-side Matrix # CR 328 A
        - Santamaria, Mongo - El bravo!, 1974; SR-24154; Santamaria, Mongo (Box 422)
          Catalog # CLT 7074; A-side Matrix # CLT7074 AS-1B
          Caliente
        - Santana - Santana, 1969; SR-24155; Santana (Box 422)
          Catalog # CS 9781; A-side Matrix # XSM139377-1E
        - Santana - Maria Maria, 1998; SR-24156; Santana; Product G&B (Box 422)
          In same jacket as # SR-24157. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 07822-13774-1; A-side Matrix # 07822-13774-1-SA
          Arista
        - Santana - Maria Maria, 1998; SR-24157; Santana; Product G&B (Box 422)
          In same jacket as # SR-24156. 2 copies.
        - Santana - Say it again, 1985; SR-24158; Santana (Box 422)
          Catalog # 44-05168; A-side Matrix # XSS 173318 1A
        - Santana - Corazon espinado (a thorn in my heart), 2000; SR-24159; Santana; Maná (Box 422)
          Catalog # ARDP-3850; A-side Matrix # ARDP-3850-SA
        - Sanatana, Carlos - Carlos Santana & Buddy Miles! Live!, 1972; SR-24160; Sanatana, Carlos; Miles, Buddy (Box 422)
          Catalog # KC 31308; A-side Matrix # PAL 31308-1D
        - Santana - Abraxas, 1985; SR-24161; Santana (Box 422)
          Catalog # PC 30130; A-side Matrix # P AL 30130-2AD
        - Santana - Abraxas, 1985; SR-24162; Santana (Box 423)
          Catalog # PC 30130; A-side Matrix # KC-30130-A
        - Santana - 25 hits (disc one), 1978; SR-24163; Santana (Box 423)
          In same jacket as # SR-24164. Double album.
          Catalog # CBS 88285; A-side Matrix # 01-88285-2A-1
          CBS
          Netherlands
        - Santana - 25 hits (disc two), 1978; SR-24164; Santana (Box 423)
          In same jacket as # SR-24163. Double album.
          Catalog # CBS 88285; A-side Matrix # 01-88285-3C-1
        - Santana - Santana's greatest hits, 1974; SR-24165; Santana (Box 423)
          Catalog # PC 33050; A-side Matrix # P AL-33050-1C
        - Santana, Juelz - There it go (the whistle song), 2005; SR-24166; Santana, Juelz (Box 423)
          Catalog # DEFR 16366-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16366-1-1
          Def Jam Recordings
        - Santana, Juelz - What the game's been missing! (disc one), 2005; SR-24167; Santana, Juelz (Box 423)
          In same jacket as # SR-24168; SR-24169. Triple album.
          Catalog # B0005426-01; A-side Matrix # B0005426-01-LP01-A3
        - Santana, Juelz - What the game's been missing! (disc two), 2005; SR-24168; Santana, Juelz (Box 423)
          In same jacket as # SR-24167; SR-24169. Triple album.
          Catalog # B0005426-01; A-side Matrix # B0005426-01-LP02-A